{
    "subject": "resource/Karl_Svozil",
    "predicate": "ontology/birthPlace",
    "object": "resource/Vienna",
    "human_readable": "Karl Svozil was born in Vienna.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.869027316570282,
            "question": "Where was Karl Svozil born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7386243343353271,
            "question": "What year was Karl Svozil born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6909138560295105,
            "question": "Is Karl Svozil Austrian?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5278466939926147,
            "question": "In what city was Karl Svozil raised?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4933825731277466,
            "question": "What is Karl Svozil known for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.36415812373161316,
            "question": "Is there any information available about Karl Svozil's parents?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3555310368537903,
            "question": "What is Karl Svozil's profession?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.316775918006897,
            "question": "Does Karl Svozil have any notable siblings?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.23616278171539307,
            "question": "Where did Karl Svozil go to school?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.1501235067844391,
            "question": "Has Karl Svozil published any books or articles?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Karl Svozil was born in Vienna.",
            "html": "dbpedia_4265_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Where did Karl Svozil go to school?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4265_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Does Karl Svozil have any notable siblings?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4265_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is Karl Svozil's profession?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4265_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4265_13.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4265_14.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4265_40.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4265_43.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4265_46.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4265_53.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4265_54.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4265_61.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4265_80.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4265_83.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Based on the provided context information, I can evaluate whether the statement \"Karl Svozil was born in Vienna\" is supported by the documents.\n\nThe relevant information from the documents is:\n\n* file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_4265/re-ranker-msmarco/12.txt\n\t+ Born in 1956 in Vienna, Austria.\n* file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_4265/re-ranker-msmarco/38.txt\n\t+ Place of Birth: Vienna\n\nTherefore, the statement \"Karl Svozil was born in Vienna\" is supported by both documents.\n\nThe final answer is:\n\n```\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\nThe documents state that Karl Svozil was born in Vienna, Austria, supporting the statement that he was born in Vienna."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}